

Education

Epicode

Certificate of Completion for Full-Stack Developer program, 2023

Community College of Allegheny County

Various welding certifications, 2021

WoodHaven Care Center

Nursing Assistance State Certification, 2011

Art Institute Of Pittsburgh

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Media Arts and Animation, 2010

Gateway Sr. High School

High School Diploma, Class of 2006



Skills

Proficient in HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, ExpressJS, NodeJS, RESTful API, TypeScript, Python, SQL (Postgres), No SQL, SCRUM, AGILE, MongoDB, PostGres, Accessibility, Adobe Photoshop, Front end development, Back end development, Web development, UI/UX, Web design, Figma

I also possess soft skills such as: Active listening, Effective verbal communication, Effective written communication, Documentation, Team player, Presentations, attention to detail, fast learner, empathetic and open to different cultures and experiences, organizational skills, trouble shooting, problem solving, creative



Work Experience

IAteAMech (2022 - present)

Full-Stack Developer

Collaboration with team to deliver products that are satisfactory to client. Implementing HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, API's, and Node.js. Time management. Helping to maintain good relationships with clients. etc.

Quantum Health (2022 - 2022)

Patient Services Representative

Customer service and team work and creativity were pivotal here

RIDC Park (2021 - 2022)

Maintenance Tech/ Mechanic

Problem solving, effective communication, creativity

Genshaw Garage (2021 - 2021)

Welder

Team work, deliver projects within blueprint specs, attention to detail

Excel HealthCare (2019 - 2020)

Care Coordinator

Customer service, explaining complex issues in a simple manner

Community Life (2017 - 2019)

Activities Coordinator

Plan activities with accessibility in mind, be creative, direct small team

Paramount Senior Living (2017 - 2017)

Activities Coordinator



Courtney Hampton-Thomas

Full-stack Developer

Contact Information

Email: jaye0888@gmail.com **Phone**: +34 677 89 43 87

Address: Sant Narcis 31, Barcelona,

Barcelona 08030

GitHub: https://github.com/Champtont

Portfolio:

https://champtont.github.io/MyPortfolio/

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/courtney-hampt

on-thomas/

Personal Summary

I am a well rounded individual with an unquenchable thirst for knowledge. With a bachelor's degree from the Art Institute of Pittsburgh, 10+ years in the nursing field, and welding certifications, I still want more opportunities to grow. Thus I am seeking a career in full stack development in Spain or remote. In tech, I am finding the chance to utilize my hard skills, as well as the soft skills that I have obtained throughout my years of experience in other fields and help people. I thrive when I am invited to grow and I am always seeking an environment that thrives on adaptability, knowledge seeking, and growth as well.